Guide to the Cornell University Board of Trustees records, 1865-2001.
Cornell University Board of Trustees records
- Series IX. Minor Committees
  - Council for the New York State College of Agriculture and the Agriculture Experiment Station, 1940 - 1941 (Box 57, Folder 35-36)
    Includes publications, resume, and photograph of Michael Peech
  - Committee on Relations with Public Authorities, 1940 - 1942 (Box 57, Folder 37-42)
  - Council for the New York State College of Home Economics, 1941 - 1942 (Box 57, Folder 43-44)
  - Sub Committee on Government Relations, 1943-07 (Box 57, Folder 45)
  - Joint Meeting of Budget Committee for the Endowed Colleges and the State Colleges, 1943-05 (Box 57, Folder 46)
  - Planning and Development Committee, 1945 - 1947 (Box 57, Folder 47-50)
  - Planning and Development Committee, 1947 - 1953 (Box 58, Folder 1-5)
  - Planning and Development Committee and Administrative Group, 1948 - 1949 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Law Committee, 1947 - 1948 (Box 58, Folder 7-10)
  - Faculty-Trustee Committee, 1948-04 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Trustee Elections re: Treman, 1949 - 1950 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Board Membership Committee, 1951 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Board Membership Committee, 1959 - 1964 (Box 58, Folder 14-16)
  - Trustee Elections: Board Memberships and lists, 1945 - 1964 (Box 58, Folder 17-20)
  - Biographies for Board of Trustees, 1933 - 1964 (Box 58, Folder 21)
  - Compulsory Military Training, 1929 - 1933 (Box 58, Folder 22-27)
    Includes publications, reports, and debates
  - Business Reorganization, 1914 (Box 58, Folder 28)
  - Cornellian Council Minutes, 1909 - 1917 (Box 58, Folder 29)
  - Committee of the Semi-Centennial Celebration, 1916 (Box 58, Folder 30)
  - Arthur H. Dean Dinner, 1962 - 1963 (Box 58, Folder 31)
  - Committee on Presidential Selection--Edmund Ezra Day, 1936 (Box 58, Folder 32)
  - Committee on Inauguration of President, 1921 (Box 58, Folder 33)
- Series X. Photographs
  - Walker Cisler, Undated (Box 100, Folder 20)
  - John Collyer, Undated (Box 100, Folder 21)
  - Arthur Dean, Undated (Box 100, Folder 22)
  - Mary Donlon, Undated (Box 100, Folder 23)
  - Robert Purcell, Undated (Box 100, Folder 24)
  - Neal Stamp, 1976 (Box 100, Folder 25)
  - Presidents Perkins, Mallot, Corson, Rhodes, Rawlings, 1995 (Box 100, Folder 26)
  - Presidents Rhodes, Corson, Perkins, Mallot, 1977 (Box 100, Folder 27)
  - Board of Trustees, 1969 (Box 100, Folder 28)
  - Malott, Perkins, Carson, Rhodes at a dinner in Willard Straight Hall to celebrate Dale Corson's 80th birthday, 1994 (Mapcase-folder 1)
  - Aerial view of campus (Mapcase-folder 1)
  - Oversize Photo of the Board of Trustees, 1959 (Mapcase-folder 1)
  - Inauguration of Frank Rhodes as 9th President, November 1977 (Mapcase-folder 1)